Guide to the Sarabande Books Records, 1990-2022 RL.01137
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2008-0028), 2004-2005; 10 boxes
  - Reviews, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Advertisements, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Marketing, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Galley books, 2005 (Box 3)
  - Author files (Box 4)
    - Townsend (Box 4)
    - Pearlman (Box 4)
    - Ghost Pain (Box 4)
    - Charles Wright (Box 4)
    - Mathis (Box 4)
    - Other Electrics (Box 5)
    - Mathis (Box 5)
    - Barnes (Box 5)
    - Barnes (Box 6)
    - Shepherd (Box 6)
    - Simon Muench (Box 7)
    - Paul Shepherd (Box 7)
  - Reviews, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Advertisements, 2005 (Box 8)
  - The Writer's Almanac, 2004 January 26 (compact disc) (Box 9)
  - The Writer's Almanac, 2004 May 3 (compact disc) (Box 9)
  - Honors (Box 9)
  - Galleys (Box 9)
  - Miscellaneous files (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box 10)
  - Author files
    - Edith Pearman (Box 10)
    - Charles Wright (Box 10)
    - Ann Townsend (Box 10)
    - Eleanor Leeman (Box 10)
    - Sydney Lea (Box 10)
    - Ander Monson (Box 10)
    - Cleopatra Mathis (Box 10)
    - Yolanda Barnes (Box 10)
    - Simon Muench (Box 10)
    - Paul Shepherd (Box 10)
  - Board meetings (Box 10)
- Accession (2009-0092), 2001-2008; 8 boxes
  Addition (2009-0092) (8325 items; 11.1 lin. ft.; dated 1998-2009) includes administrative files, book reviews, press releases, author files and correspondence, and manuscripts and drafts from authors published by Sarabande.
  - Nonprofit materials (Box 1)
    - Board meeting files, 2006-2007 (Box 1)
    - Nonprofit activities, 2002-2007 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Arts Council grant applications, 2002-2006 (Box 1)
    - NEA grant applications, 2002-2008 (Box 1)
    - NEA reporting, 1998-2008 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Humanities Council applications (Box 1)
    - Travel and events, 2006 (Box 1)
  - Author files and correspondence (Box 2)
    - Poetry Out Loud, 2007-2008 (Box 2)
    - Contest finalist files, poetry and fiction (Box 2)
    - Brett Ralph (Box 2)
    - Larry Sutin (Box 2)
    - Kiki Petrosino (Box 2)
    - Paula Bohince (Box 2)
    - Dick Allen (Box 2)
    - Sallie Bingham (Box 2)
    - Monica Ferrell (Box 2)
    - Josephine Jacobsen (Box 2)
    - David Crouse (Box 2)
    - Jessie Harriman (Box 2)
    - Nana Lampton (Box 2)
    - Susan Oleksien (Box 2)
    - Debra Nystrom (Box 2)
    - Jean Valentine (Box 2)
    - Paul Yoon (Box 2)
    - Karen McElmurray (Box 3)
    - C.E. Perry (Box 3)
    - Acquisitions, 2004-2007 (Box 3)
    - Author ideas (Box 3)
  - Manuscripts
    - Skinner/Weaver, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Paul Yoon, Once the Shore final copy (Box 3)
    - Jean Valentine, Lucy (Box 3)
    - C.E. Perry, Night Works (Box 3)
    - Sallie Bingham, Transgressions (Box 3)
    - Sallie Bingham, Red Car (Box 3)
    - Rick Barot, Want (Box 3)
    - Cate Marvin, Fragments of the Head of a Queen (Box 3)
    - Dick Allen, Present Vanishing (Box 3)
    - Paula Bohince, Incident at the Edge of Bayonet Woods (Box 3)
    - Jenny Boully, The Book of Beginnings and Endings (Box 3)
    - Josephine Jacobsen, Contents of a Minute (Box 3)
    - Barry Wormser, Scattered Chapters (Box 4)
    - Salle Bingham, Red Car (Box 4)
    - Karen McElmurray, Motel of the Stars (Box 4)
    - Monica Ferrell, Beasts of the Chase (Box 4)
    - David Crouse, The Man Back There (Box 4)
  - Marketing files
    - Correspondence, 2008 (Box 4)
    - Book reviews, 2008 (Box 4)
    - Catalogue, 2008 (Box 4)
    - Pre-sales and sales conference materials (Box 5)
    - AWP Conferences, 2007-2008 (Box 5)
    - Press releases (Box 5)
    - Book reviews (Box 6)
  - Binders
    - Cate Marvin, World's Tallest Disaster, 2001 (Box 6)
    - Rick Barot, The Darker Fall, 2002 (Box 6)
    - These Hands I Know, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Sallie Bingham, Transgressions, 2002 (Box 6)
    - Kiki DeLancey, Coal Miner's Holiday, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Alyce Miller, Season of the Body, 2002 (Box 7)
    - Debra Nystrom, Torn Sky, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Kate Gadbow, Pushed to Shove, 2003 (Box 7)
    - Dick Allen, The Day Before, 2003 (Box 7)
    - James Tate, Lost River, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Sharon Bryan and William Olsen, Planet on the Table, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Sharon Solwitz, Bloody Mary, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Marjorie Sandor, Portrait of My Mother Who Posed Nude in Wartime, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Mark Turpin, Hammer, 2003 (Box 8)
    - Carrie Comer, The Unrequested, 2003 (Box 8)
- Accession (2010-0028), 2001-2010, 8 boxes
  Addition (2010-0028) (9000 items; 12.0 lin. ft.; dated 2001-2010) includes administrative files, Sarabande correspondence with authors, author files, poetry and fiction finalists, and various book reviews and advertisements.
  - Sarah G's files, board meetings 2006-2009, miscellaneous correspondence (Box 1)
    - Interns, 2003-2008 (Box 1)
    - Summer interns (Box 1)
    - Katie Byrum, intern (Box 1)
    - Interns, general (Box 1)
    - Job hunt, Betsey (Box 1)
    - Erika Lunobom (Box 1)
    - Abbie Gramig (Box 1)
    - Interns: Kate Whetzel (Box 1)
    - Cathy Rogers, intern (Box 1)
    - Loren Jaggers, intern (Box 1)
    - Chris Carpenter (Box 1)
    - Tim Moran (Box 1)
    - Student poetry prize, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Rotary Club, 2006 February 7 (Box 1)
    - Incoming and outgoing letters, 2009 January-November (17 folders) (Box 1)
    - Nickole's Transition (Box 1)
    - The big read (Box 1)
    - 15th anniversary party (Box 1)
    - Fall parties (Box 1)
    - KHC 2005 (Box 1)
    - KY Foundation for Women, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Eric Mathieu Application (Box 1)
    - NY community Trust (Box 1)
    - Nana Lampton (Box 1)
    - AL Lyons meeting, April 2005 (Box 1)
    - Pat Owen (Box 1)
    - Annie Axton (Box 1)
    - Sallie Bingham letters, 2001-2003 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Board meetings, 2006-2009 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Non-profit activities, 2008-2009 (Box 1)
  - Author files (Box 2)
    - Acquisitions, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
    - Poetry finalists, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Fiction finalists, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Heather Sellers (Box 2)
    - Ralph Angel (Box 2)
    - Face First, Face Facts (Box 2)
    - Manuscript: A Family of Strangers by Deborah Tall (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Family of Strangers corrections (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Exceptions and Melancholies: Poems, 1986-2006, Ralph Angel manuscript (Box 2)
    - Ralph Angel poems (Box 2)
    - Proofs: Friesens for Purpura (Box 2)
    - Lia Purpura (Box 2)
    - Originals: Lorca/Angel in Spanish and English, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Manuscript: My Psychic (Box 2)
    - Purpura original manuscript (Box 2)
    - Final copy: On Looking Essays, by Lia Purpura (Box 2)
    - Pinsky (Box 2)
    - Kimbrell, published 2006 (Box 2)
    - Shirley, Dark Familiar (Box 2)
  - Author files (Box 3)
    - Legitimate Dangers, first corrected proofs (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Horror Vacui by Thomas Heise (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Susan Richards (5 folders) (Box 3)
    - Connecting Lines (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Mexican anthology (Box 3)
    - Líneas Conectados (Box 3)
    - English originals (Box 3)
    - Aleda Shirley (Box 3)
    - Robert Pinsky, First Things (Box 3)
    - Lorca legal stuff (Box 3)
    - Deborah Tall (Box 3)
    - Ralph Angel correspondence and poems (Box 3)
  - Author files, correspondence, marketing (Box 4)
    - Incoming and outgoing correspondence, 2006(22 folders) (Box 4)
    - Legitimate Dangers, Dumanis Marvin (Box 4)
    - Legitimate permissions (Box 4)
    - Mexico/U.S. correspondence (Box 4)
    - Hanging in the Foaling Barn (Box 4)
    - My Psychic, James Kimbrell (Box 4)
    - Lia Purpura: writings, correspondence (Box 4)
    - Draft: On Looking Essays by Lia Purpura (Box 4)
    - Angel/Lorca Translation (Box 4)
    - AWP Austin, 2006 (Box 4)
    - Sales/pre-sales, 2006 (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Ads (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous marketing (Box 4)
    - First annuals student poetry competition (Box 4)
    - Honors (Box 4)
    - Want, Barot (Box 4)
    - Reviews (Box 4)
  - Author files, financial information (Box 5)
    - Jenny Boully (Box 5)
    - Water: Nine Stories (5 folders) (Box 5)
    - Mexico/U.S. agreement (Box 5)
    - Mexico/U.S. fundraiser (Box 5)
    - Marvin fragment (Box 5)
    - Preacher, Stern (Box 5)
    - Epistles, Jarman (Box 5)
    - California transit (Box 5)
    - Book of Beginnings and Endings (Box 5)
    - Payroll tax, 2007 (Box 5)
    - 990 PF, 2007 (Box 5)
    - Financial statements, 2007 (Box 5)
    - Donations, 2007 (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Author files, correspondence (Box 6)
    - Matthew Lippman (Box 6)
    - Patsy Vigderman (Box 6)
    - A Thousand Trifles, June 2005 (Box 6)
    - To read Sallie's stories (Box 6)
    - Sallie's memoir (Box 6)
    - Sallie's essays (Box 6)
    - Sallie's stories maybe (Box 6)
    - Baron Wormser, number 4 (Box 6)
    - Scattered chapters (Box 6)
    - Rick Barot (Box 6)
    - Extra material-Boully (Box 6)
    - Alyce Miller (Box 6)
    - Incoming and outgoing correspondence, 2007 (24 folders) (Box 6)
    - Phil Levine/Jaime Sabines (Box 6)
    - Diane Lefer (Box 6)
    - Maybe/Carew stories (Box 6)
    - Gabriel Fried (Box 6)
    - Cats Marvin: Head of a Queen (Box 6)
    - Jenny Boully (Box 6)
    - Epistles by Mark Jarman (Box 6)
    - Gerald Stern/The Preacher (Box 6)
    - Jan Carew (5 folders) (Box 6)
  - Author files, correspondence, publication production binders (Box 7)
    - Making the New Lamb Take by Gabriel Fried (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - California Transit by Diane Lefer (3 folders) (Box 7)
    - Diane Lefer correspondence (Box 7)
    - Translation: Tarumba by Jaime Sabines (Box 7)
    - Tarumba corrections (Box 7)
    - Philip Levine correspondence (Box 7)
    - The Memory Place of Isabella Stewart Gardner by Patricia Vigderman (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - The New Year of Yellow by Matthew Lippman (Box 7)
    - Air Fare: Stories, Poems, and Essays on Flight (Box 7)
    - They Have a Word for It by Howard Rheingold (Box 7)
    - Air Fare: fiction and CNF (Box 7)
    - Air Fare: poetry (Box 7)
    - Air Fare: miscellaneous (Box 7)
    - Subject Matter by Baron Wormser (Box 7)
    - PeeWee settlement (Box 7)
    - A Taste of the Sweet Apple by Jo Anna Holt-Watson (Box 7)
    - Green Wheat translated by Zack Rogow (Box 7)
  - Books and publications, miscellaneous reviews and ads (Box 8)
    - 12 books (Box 8)
    - Publications, 2005-2007 (7 folders) (Box 8)
  - Art Disk (AirFare) digital files, 2003; One CD-R containing 2 .tiff files and one .psd (151 MB total) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
- Accession (2011-0076), 1994-2011, 8 boxes and 1 oversize folder
  Addition (2011-0076) (6750 items; 9.0 lin. ft.; dated 1994-2011) includes materials from conferences, non-profit activities, grants, correspondence, marketing, staffing, finances, and author files.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Financial and budget materials are CLOSED until 2036. These have been removed to Box 8 of this accession.
  - Conferences 2010 (Box 1)
    - Pre-sales/Sales Spring-Summer 2011 (Box 1)
    - Pre-sales Conference FW 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    - Pre-sales/Sales Spring-Summer 2010 (Box 1)
    - Pre-sales Conference May 2009 (Box 1)
    - Pre-sales/Sales Spring 2009 (Fall 2008) (Box 1)
    - Association of Writers and Writing Programs (AWP) Denver, 2010 (Box 1)
    - Association of Writers and Writing Programs (AWP) Denver, 2009 (Box 1)
    - NonfictioNow, 1-3 November 2007 (Box 1)
    - Accessibility Documents (Box 1)
  - Non-Profit Activities 2010
    - Non-Profit Activities, 2010 (Box 1)
    - Editor for a Day Workshop (Box 1)
    - University of Louisville Women's Festival of the Book, May 2010 (Box 1)
    - Flo Gault Prize, 2010 (Box 1)
    - Flo Gault Poetry Prize, 2009 (Box 1)
    - Projects for Summer 2007 (Box 1)
  - Grant Reports/Applications 2010
    - Kentucky Arts Council (KAC) Partnership, 2009 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Arts Council (KAC) Partnership Report, 2009-1010 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Arts Council (KAC) Partnership, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Arts Council (KAC) Partnership Report, 2008 (Box 1)
    - General Operating Support No. 1 Grant Report, 2007-2008 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Humanitites Council (KHC) Major Grant Application, 2005 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Application, 2008-2009 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Report, 30 June 2009 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Report, 2009-2010 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Application, 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Report, 2010-2011 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky American Recovery and Reinvestment Act, 2009 (Box 1)
    - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) Application Recovery Act (Box 1)
  - Correspondence 2010
    - Letters, January-November 2010, 10 folders, in reverse order (Box 1)
    - Bingham, Sallie, 2004-2006, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Dante Portfolio, 2008 (Box 1)
    - McGlynn, Karyna, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Gabriel, Jerry, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Muench, Simone, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Bursky, Rick, 2009 (Box 1)
    - Wright, Charles Outtakes, 2009 (Box 1)
    - Butler, Jane Ashley, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Yoon, Paul, 2008 (Box 2)
    - What Falls Between, undated (Box 2)
    - Taylor, Alex, 2010 (Box 2)
    - Lerman, Eleanor No. 3 (Box 2)
    - Story, Julia (Box 2)
    - Monson, Ander (Box 2)
    - Vaswani, Neela No. 2, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Vaswani, Neela, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Vaswani, Neela: You Have Given Me a Country (Box 2)
    - McQuade, Molly, 2010 (Box 2)
  - Marketing Materials
    - One Word Marketing (Box 2)
    - Sallie Bingham's New Stories (Box 2)
    - Film Rights (Box 2)
    - Old Fundraising Letters (Box 2)
    - Publicity Ideas (Box 2)
    - Publishing/Reading Trends (Box 2)
    - Perseus Book Group (Box 2)
    - Royalty Statements, 2007-2009, 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Subrights 2006-2009, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Contest Finalists
    - Mary Macarthy Prize in Fiction Finalists, 2010 (Box 2)
    - Kathryn A. Morton Prize in Poetry Finalists, 2010 (Box 2)
    - Mary Macarthy Prize in Fiction Finalists, 2007 (Box 2)
  - Staffing, 2009-2010 (Box 3)
    - McGrath, Kristina (Box 3)
    - Pascoe, Jeanette (Box 3)
    - Lesousky, Benjamin (Box 3)
    - Woods, Jen (Box 3)
    - Brown, Nickole (Box 3)
    - Contest Staffing 2009 (Box 3)
    - First Readers, Evaluations (Box 3)
    - Interns, 2010 (Box 3)
    - Authors' Photos, 5 folders (Box 3)
  - Reviews, 2009, 5 folders (Box 3)
    Additional materials are in Oversize Folder 1.
  - Pewee-Watson Dispute
    - Watson E-mails, 2004 (Box 3)
    - General Marketing for Watson, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Board Documents
    - Official Board Meetings (Box 3)
    - Board Meeting, 21 November 2010 (Box 3)
    - Board Meeting, May 2010 (Box 3)
    - Board Meeting, Fall 2009 (Box 3)
  - Author Files
    - Gluck, Louise, April 2004 (Box 3)
    - Jarman, Mark, July 2004 (Box 3)
    - Sellers, Heather, May 2001, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Vaswani, Neela, January 2004, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Leung, Brian, April 2004, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Vogelsang, Arthur, October 2003, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - McQuade, Molly, April 1999, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Cramer, Steven, October 2004, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Monson, Ander, May 2005, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Lee, Karen An-hwei, October 2005 (Box 4)
    - Muench, Simone, November 2005, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Wing, Catherine, October 2005 (Box 4)
    - McGlynn, Karyna, May 2009 (Box 4)
    - Ralph, Brett Eugene, March 2009 (Box 4)
    - Butler, Ashley, April 2009 (Box 5)
    - Petrosino, Kirk, January 2009 (Box 5)
    - Sutin, Lawrence, November 2008, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Nystrom, Debra, June 2008 (Box 5)
    - Story, Julia, November 2009 (Box 5)
    - Monson, Ander, January 2010 (Box 5)
    - Bursky, Rick, May 2010 (Box 5)
    - McQuade, Molly, March 2010, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Pinky, Robert; Mazur, Michael (Dante), 2009 (Box 5)
    - Muench, Simone, November 2009 (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Alex, September 2009, 2 of 4 folders (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Alex, September 2009, Folders 3 and 4 of 4 (Box 6)
    - Lerman, Eleanor, September 2009 (Box 6)
    - Vaswani, Neela, February 2010, 1 of 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Vaswani, Neela, February 2010, 2 to 4 of 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Gabriel, Jerry, August 2009, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - CLOSED UNTIL 2036: Big-Picture Financials (Box 8)
    - Financial Balances and Quarterly Reports, 2008-2010 (Box 8)
    - 990 Tax Return 2010 (Box 8)
    - Audited Financial Statements 2009-2010 (Box 8)
    - Budget Remaining 2009 (Box 8)
    - Budget 2009 (Box 8)
    - Budget 2010 (Box 8)
  - Author reviews archives, 2010, 4 folders (Box 9)
  - Large-Project documents:
    - Pie Party (Box 9)
    - Catalog, 2009-2011 (Box 9)
    - Newsletters, 2009-2010 (Box 9)
  - Author events, 2000-2006 (Box 9)
  - Author Binders (rehoused into folders)
    - Townsend, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Wright (Box 9)
    - Mathis, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Barnes, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Lerman, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Lea, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Pearlman, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Shepherd, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Reviews, 2009 (4 items) (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Large-Project documents: School for the Blind poetry workshop (Oversize-folder 2)
- Accession (2012-0046), 2006-2011, 9 boxes
  - Correspondence, January-July 2011 (Box 1)
  - Foundation research and correspondence (Box 1)
    - Brown-Forman Corp (Box 1)
    - Brown-Forman Corp, 2006 (Box 1)
    - Brown-Forman Corp, 2008 (Box 1)
    - James Graham Brown (Box 1)
    - Creative Capital Foundation (Box 1)
    - The Horn Foundation (Box 1)
    - Edith Gardner Foundation (Box 1)
    - Furthermore Foundation (Box 1)
    - KFW Stuff (Box 1)
    - Michigan trip (Box 1)
    - Chapbook Series talk (Box 1)
    - PW essay (Box 1)
    - Nonfiction/Iowa, March 2010 (Box 1)
  - Non-profit activities (Box 2)
  - First West (Box 2)
  - Rodney Jack (Box 2)
  - 21c Reading Series (Box 2)
  - Nonfiction Now Conference, November 2010 (Box 2)
  - AWP 2011, Washington D.C. (Box 2)
  - Sales Conference, March 2011 (Box 2)
  - Pre-Sales Conference, June and November 2011 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous solicitation events (Box 2)
  - Royalty Reports, 2010 (Box 3)
  - Subrights, 2010 (Box 3)
  - Articles about our authors (Box 3)
  - Articles about Sarabande (Box 3)
  - Prizes through 2011 (Box 3)
  - Writers Almanac CDs (4) (Box 3)
  - Reviews, 2011 (Box 3)
  - Author files (Box 3)
    - Fleischmann/Syzygy, Beauty (Box 3)
    - Skinner/7 Habits of Highly Effective Poets (Box 3)
    - Lee/Something In My Eye (Box 4)
    - Van Meter/If You Knew Then What I Know Now (Box 4)
    - Davis/The Cows (Box 4)
    - Mullins/Greetings from Below (Box 4)
    - Jarman/Bone Fires (Box 4)
    - Horrocks/This Is Not Your City (Box 4)
    - Ossip/The Cold War (Box 5)
    - Hernandez/Hoodwinked (Box 5)
    - Bingham/Mending: New & Selected (Box 5)
    - Wade/Small Fires (Box 5)
  - Acquisitions (Box 5)
  - Decano Book (Box 6)
  - Mary McCarthy Fiction Prize, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Kathryn A Morton, 2011 (Box 6)
  - September Submissions, 2011 (Box 6)
  - Manuscripts (Box 6)
    - Skinner/6.5 Habits (Box 6)
    - Lee/Something In My Eye (Box 6)
    - Mullins/Greetings from Below (Box 7)
    - Bohince/The Children (Box 7)
    - Purpura/Rough Likeness (Box 7)
    - Fleischmann/Syzygy, Beauty (Box 8)
    - Wade/Small Fires (In Lieu of Flowers) (Box 8)
    - Bingham/Mending: New & Selected (Box 8)
    - Horrocks/This Is Not Your City (Box 8)
    - Hernandez/Hoodwinked (Box 8)
    - Van Meter/If You Knew Then What I Know Now (Box 9)
- Accession (2013-0158), 2006-2012, 5 boxes
  - Author binders
    - McElmurray, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Allen, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Ferrell, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Crouse, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Bohince, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Wormser, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Jacobsen, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Bingham, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Barot, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Miller, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Boully, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Levine, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Fried, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Mexican-American Anthology, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Kimbrell, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Carew, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Marvin, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Jarman, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Stern, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Dumanis and Marvin, 2006 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Mexican-American Anthology permissions, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Tall, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Angel, 2006 (Box 2)
    - Lorca, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Purpura, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Heise, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Richards, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Shirley, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Pinsky, 2006 (Box 3)
    - Leer, 2007 (Box 3)
    - Vigderman, 2007 (Box 3)
    - Lippman, 2007 (Box 3)
  - Reviews and manuscripts
    - Reviews (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Binder/Rise (Box 4)
    - Shapiro/Easy Math (Box 4)
    - Vigderman/Possibility (Box 4)
    - Passarello/Let Me Clear My Throat (Box 4)
    - Cramer/Clangings (Box 4)
    - Mathis/Book of Dog (Box 4)
    - Heise/Moth (Box 4)
    - Dwyer/Belle Laid (Box 4)
    - Orr/City of Poetry (Box 4)
    - Wing/Gin and Bleach (Box 4)
    - Kasischke/If a Stranger (Box 4)
  - Administrative materials and author correpondence
    - Staffing, grants, and administrative documentation (12 folders) (Box 5)
    - Author correspondence (5 folders) (Box 5)
  - Ride to Life - a short film (.m4v), 2011; CD-R containing one MP4 (.m4v) video file (587 MB) (Digital-materials RL01137-SET-0001)
- Accession (2014-0150), 2008-2014; 2 boxes
  - Administrative materials and author correspondence
    - Acquisitions, 2012-2014 (Box 1)
    - Flo Gault, 2012 (Box 1)
    - Fiction contest finalists, 2013 (Box 1)
    - Kentucky Literature Series, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Letters of correspondence, 2013 (Box 1)
    - Catalog, 2014 (Box 2)
    - Newsletter, 2013 (Box 2)
    - Author clippings (Box 2)
  - Foundation research and correspondence
    - South Arts (Box 1)
    - Starbucks (Box 1)
    - Literary Ventures Fund (Box 1)
    - Lannan Foundation (Box 1)
    - Brown-Forman, 2009-2011 (Box 1)
  - Author files
    - Heise/Moth (Box 2)
    - Dolven/Speculative Music (Box 2)
    - Petrosino/Hymn for the Black Terrific (Box 2)
    - Williams/Catherine's Laughter (Box 2)
    - Branscum, Thomas/Red Holler (Box 2)
    - Friedman/Fire Year (Box 2)
  - Reviews
    - 1997-2013 (Box 3)
- Accession (2015-0151), 2009-2015, 3 boxes
  - Author files
    - Turpin, Mark/Hammer (Box 1)
    - Bingham, Sallie/Transgressions and Red Car (Box 1)
    - Leung, Brian/World Famous Love Acts (Box 1)
    - Howley, Kerry/Thrown (Box 1)
    - Bingham, Sallie/Blue Box (Box 1)
    - Minor, Kyle/Praying Drunk (Box 1)
    - Muench, Simone/Wolf Centos (Box 1)
    - Stewart, Angela (Pelster)/Limber (Box 1)
    - Hemenway, Arna Bontemps/Elegy on Kinderklavier (Box 1)
    - Martinez, David/Hustle (Box 1)
    - Dunn, Stephen/Keeper of Limits (Box 1)
    - Walter, Wendy, Multiply/Divide (Box 1)
    - Barot, Rick/Chord (Box 1)
    - Griner, Paul/Hurry Please, I Want to Know (Box 1)
    - Bishop, Sean/The Night We're Not Sleeping In (Box 1)
    - Ossip, Kathy/The Do-Over (Box 1)
    - Poole, Nathan/Father Brother Keeper (Box 1)
    - Hannick, Riley/Three Kinds of Motion (Gravel Ends) (Box 1)
    - Day, Adam/A Model of a City in Civil War (Box 1)
  - Author binders, 2009-2010
    - C E Perry (Box 1)
    - Valentine (Box 1)
    - Nystrom (Box 1)
    - Yoon (Box 2)
    - Sutin (Box 2)
    - Ralph (Box 2)
    - Petrosino (Box 2)
    - Butler (Box 2)
    - McQuade (Box 2)
    - McGlynn (Box 2)
    - Gabriel (Box 2)
    - Pinsky (Box 2)
    - Muench (Box 2)
    - Lerman (Box 2)
    - Taylor (Box 2)
    - Monson (Box 2)
    - Bursky (Box 2)
    - Wright (Box 3)
  - Administrative Materials, 2012-2015
    - Board meetings, 2012-2014 (Box 3)
    - Murray reading/panel (Box 3)
    - EKU Conference (Box 3)
    - Lit salon/Greaves (Box 3)
    - Lubbock visit (Box 3)
    - Small Press Award (Box 3)
    - AWP Boston (Box 3)
    - Interns, 2014-2015 (Box 3)
    - Flo Gault, 2013 (Box 3)
    - Non-profit, 2013 (Box 3)
    - AWP small press judging (Box 3)
    - Pie Party, 2013 (Box 3)
    - Kentucky Arts, 2011-2012 (Box 3)
    - NEA application, 2012-2013 (Box 3)